A Finding Aid to the C. J. (Clarence Joseph) Bulliet Papers, circa 1888-1959, in the Archives of American Art AAA.bullclar
Archives of American Art
- Artist Files, 1919-1952; Series 4; 20 Linear feet Boxes 5-24
  - Pinto, Salvatore, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Pinturicchio, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Pippin, Horace, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Pirola, Louis, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Pisarewska-Karmi, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Pisarro, Camille, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Plaschke, Paul A., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Plath, Karl, 1932-1935 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Pleimling, Winnifred, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Pleissner, Ogden, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Podchernikoff, Alexis M., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Poe, Hugh M., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Pogany, Willy, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Polasek, Albin, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Pollack, A. L., 1939 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Pollaiuolo, Antonio del, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Pollard, James, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Pollet, Joseph, 1928-1929 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Pollock, Merlin, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Pomi, Alessandro, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Ponsen, Tunis, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Pontormo, Jacapo Carpussi, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Poole, Abram, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Poole, Burnell, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Poole, Frederick V., 1927 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Poor, Henry Varnum, 1932-1936 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Portinari, Candido, 1935-1940 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Possoz, Mily, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Post, Herman, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Postle, Joy, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Pothast, B., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Potter, Myron, 1928 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Potter, William J., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Potthast, Edward A., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Pottner, Emil, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Potts, J. C., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Potts, Sherman, 1929 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Poucelet, Maurice Georges, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Pougheon, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Pougialis, Constantine, 1932-1935 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Poulbot, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Poull, Mary B., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Poundstone, George C., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Pousette-Dart, Nathaniel, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Poussin, Nicolas, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Powers, Mary E., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Poynter, Edward J., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Prampolini, Enrico, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Pratt, John, 1935-1936 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Prax, Valentine, 1930 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Prendergast, Charles, 1935-1937 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Prendergast, Maurice B., 1932-1934 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Pressoir, Esther, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - Preussl, Carl, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - Prevost, Audrey, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - Price, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - Price, Chester, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - Pricket, Helen, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - Prini, G., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 70)
  - Privato, Cosimo, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - Procter, Dod, 1926-1930 (Box 19, Folder 72)
  - Prohaska, R. J., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 73)
  - Protier, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 74)
  - Prud'hom, P. P., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 75)
  - Pruna, Pedro, 1928-1935 (Box 19, Folder 76)
  - Prusheck, Gregory, 1925-1932 (Box 19, Folder 77)
  - Pryde, James, 1929 (Box 19, Folder 78)
  - Pryor, Yvonne, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 79)
  - Pushman, Housep, 1937-1952 (Box 19, Folder 80)
  - Quaedslieg, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 81)
  - Quintanilla, Luis, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 82)
  - Quirt, Nicholas J., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 83)
  - Quirt, Walter W., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 84)
  - Rackham, Arthur, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 85)
  - Radenkovitch, Yovan, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 86)
  - Radice, Canio, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 87)
  - Raeburn, Henry, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 88)
  - Raemaekers, Louis, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 89)
  - Raffaelle, Jean François, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 90)
  - Rafferty, Howard, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 91)
  - Rajor, Paul, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 92)
  - Ranger, Henry W., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 93)
  - Ranken, William B. E., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 94)
  - Raphael, 1928 (Box 19, Folder 95)
  - Raplin, Grace, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 96)
  - Raskin, Saul, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 97)
  - Rauschert, J. Karl, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 98)
  - Rausey, A., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 99)
  - Rawson, Carl Wendell, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 100)
  - Ray, Man, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 101)
  - Raymond, Frank, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 102)
  - Raynaud, Louis, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 103)
  - Rea, James, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 104)
  - Read, William, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 105)
  - Rebay, Hilla, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 106)
  - Rebour, F., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 107)
  - Recchia, Richard H., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 108)
  - Reckitt, Charles C., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 109)
  - Redfield, Edward W., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 110)
  - Redon, Odilon, 1936-1941 (Box 19, Folder 111)
  - Reed, Doel, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 112)
  - Reed, Earl H., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 113)
  - Reed, Fred, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 114)
  - Reentz, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 115)
  - Reeves-Smith, H., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 116)
  - Refregier, Anton, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 117)
  - Rehr, A. Stuart, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 118)
  - Reichmann, Josephine L., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 119)
  - Reid, John R., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 120)
  - Reid, O. Richard, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 121)
  - Reid, Robert, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 122)
  - Reiffel, Charles, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 123)
  - Reinitz, Maximilian, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 124)
  - Reisner, Irma, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 125)
  - Reiss, Lionel S., 1924-1925 (Box 19, Folder 126)
  - Reiss, Winold, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 127)
  - Reitzel, Marques E., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 128)
  - Rekuchi, Michael, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 129)
  - Remahl, Frederick, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 130)
  - Rembrandt Harmensz van Rijn, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 131)
  - Remington, Frederic, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 132)
  - Remisoff, Nicolas, 1928-1938 (Box 19, Folder 133)
  - Remmert, E., 1931 (Box 19, Folder 134)
  - Remor, B., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 135)
  - Remski, Stanislaw, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 136)
  - Remson, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 137)
  - Reni, Guido, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Reno-Hassenberg, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Renoir, Auguste, 1930-1941 (Box 20, Folder 3-5)
  - Resler, George, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Rethel, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Revere, Paul, 1929 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Revold, Axel, 1930 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Reyn, Jan de, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Reynolds, Joshua, 1928 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Reynolds, Wellington Jared, 1935 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Ribera (?), circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Ribot, Augustin T., circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Ricco, Andrea, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Ricco, Martin, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Rice, Adele, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Rice, Perry, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Rich, George, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Richard, Jacob, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Richards, Lucy Currier, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Richards, Myra, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Richardson, Constance C., 1940 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Richardson, Esther Ruble, 1937-1941 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Richardson, J., circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Richey, Oakley E., circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Richmond, Leondard, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Richter, H. H., circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Richter, Hans Theo, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Richter, Mary, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Richter, Susan, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Rider, Arthur G., circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Riesener, Henri François, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Rigaud, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Riggs, Robert, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Rikucki, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Riou, Louis, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Ripley, Arden Lassell, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Ripley, Lucy Perkins, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Rippingille, E. V., circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Risque, Caroline, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Ritman, Louis, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Ritman, Maurice, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Ritschel, William, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Rittinberg, Henry R., circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Rivera, Diego, 1939-1940 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Rivere, Raymond Briton, 1931 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Robert, Hubert, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Roberti, Romodo, 1934-1935 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Roberts, Jessie Macy, 1931 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Roberts, William, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Robertson, Jack, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Robetta, Cristofiva, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Robins, W. P., 1927 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Robinson, Boardman, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Robinson, Heath, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Robinson, Increase, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Robinson, Theodore, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Robinson, William S., circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Rodin, Auguste, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Roe, Frederick Rushing, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Roecker, H. Leon, 1927 (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - Roerich, Nicholas, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - Roerich, Svetoslav, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - Rofs, Felicien, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - Rohricht, Wolf, 1929 (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - Rojdesvensky, Basil, 1930 (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - Rollo, Joseph, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - Rolshoven, Julius, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - Romagnoli, Carlo, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - Romagnoli, Giovanni, 1930 (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - Romanelli, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 72)
  - Romano, Emmanuel, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - Romano, Umberto, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 74)
  - Romero, Carlos Orozco, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 75)
  - Romney, George, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - Rondinelli, Niccolo, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 77)
  - Ronnebeck, Arnold, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 78)
  - Rook, Edward F., circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 79)
  - Roosmalen-Juesnel, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 80)
  - Ropp, Herbert, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 81)
  - Rose, Francis, 1934-1939 (Box 20, Folder 82)
  - Rosenbauer, Wallace W., circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 83)
  - Rosenberg, Cecil, 1939-1940 (Box 20, Folder 84)
  - Rosenberg, H. M., circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 85)
  - Rosenburg, Louis C., 1933 (Box 20, Folder 86)
  - Rosenshine, Annette, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 87)
  - Rosenthal, Bernard J., 1939 (Box 20, Folder 88)
  - Rosenthal, Doris, 1937-1939 (Box 20, Folder 89)
  - Rosier, George, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 90)
  - Rosin, Harry, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 91)
  - Ross, Torey, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 92)
  - Rosseau, Percival, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 93)
  - Rosselli, Cosimo, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 94)
  - Rossi, Francesco Dei, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 95)
  - Rosso, Merdardo, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 96)
  - Roszak, Theodore J., 1933-1938 (Box 20, Folder 97)
  - Roth, Frederick G. R., circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 98)
  - Rothenberg, Arthur, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 99)
  - Rothenstein, William, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 100)
  - Rouault, Georges, 1933-1941 (Box 20, Folder 101)
  - Rous, Helen Woods, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 102)
  - Rousseau, Henri, 1931-1936 (Box 20, Folder 103)
  - Rousseau, Theodore, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 104)
  - Roussel, K. X., 1926 (Box 20, Folder 105)
  - Rousseff, W. Vladimir, 1932 (Box 20, Folder 106)
  - Roux, G. L., circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 107)
  - Rowlandson, Thomas, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 108)
  - Roy, Pierre, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 109)
  - Rubczak, Jean, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 110)
  - Rubens, Peter Paul, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 111)
  - Rubenstein, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 112)
  - Rubio, Timoteo Perez, 1929 (Box 20, Folder 113)
  - Rudnay, Gyula, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 114)
  - Ruellan, Andree, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 115)
  - Ruemann, Alexandra Victoria, 1929 (Box 20, Folder 116)
  - Ruggiero, Generoso, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 117)
  - Ruiz, Jose, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 118)
  - Rumbold, Hugo, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 119)
  - Rumsey, Daniel Lockwood, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 120)
  - Rungius, Carl, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 121)
  - Rupprecht, Edgar A., circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 122)
  - Rush, Olive, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 123)
  - Rushbury, Henry, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 124)
  - Russell, Charles M., circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 125)
  - Russell, George, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 126)
  - Russell, James L., circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 127)
  - Russell, John, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 128)
  - Russmann, Felix, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 129)
  - Rustad, Roland, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 130)
  - Rutland, Violet, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 131)
  - Ruvolo, Felix, 1940 (Box 20, Folder 132)
  - Ryback, J., circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 133)
  - Ryder, Albert Pinkham, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 134)
  - Ryder, Arthur, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 135)
  - Ryder, Chauncy F., circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 136)
  - Ryerson, Margery, circa 1888-1959 (Box 20, Folder 137)
  - Saeddeleer, Valerius de, 1929 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - St. Mart, Baroness de, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Salemme, Antonio, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Salietti, Alberto, 1936 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Salisbury, Frank O., 1927-1938 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Salla, Salvatore, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Salter, John, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Sample, Paul, 1936-1941 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Sanders, Bernard, 1936 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Sanders, Manning, 1929 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Sandkuhl, Hermann, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Sandona, Matteo, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Sandzen, Birger, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Sanford, Edward Field, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Sanford, George F., 1947 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Sanger, H. L., circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Sangroniz, Alberto de, 1929 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Sardeau, Helene, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Sarff, Walter, 1930 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Sargent, John Singer, 1933-1941 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Sargent, Margaret, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Sargent, Walter, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Sarrat, Verge, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Sartorius, J. N., circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Sassetta, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Sater, Miles, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Sauchon, Marion, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Saunders, Theodore, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Saunty, Alfred de, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Savage, Edward, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Savage, Eugene F., circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Savage, Frances, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Saverys, Albert, 1928-1935 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Savreux, Maurice, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Sawyer, Conway, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Sawyer, Phil, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Schade, Harald, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Schaeffer, Samuel Bernard, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Schaetzel, M., 1939 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Schaper, Wolfgang, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Schatz, Bezalel, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Schatz, Boris, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Schauman, Ruth, 1930 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Scheibe, Richard, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Scheinman, Esther, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Schell, Gertrude, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Schewshenko, Taras, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Schiavone, Andrea, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Schiling, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Schnakenberg, H. E., circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Schnel, Mrs. B. Hermont, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Schlaikjer, J. W., circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Schlein, Charles, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Schmid, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Schmidt, Felix, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Schmidt, Frank J., 1939 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Schmidt, Katherine, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Schmidt, Oscar, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Schmidt-Rottluff, Karl, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - Schmied, F. L., circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - Schmitt, Carl, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Schmitz, Carl L., 1939 (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Schofield, Flora, 1929-1939 (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - Scholz, Belle Kinney and Leopold Scholz, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - Schongauer, Martin, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - Schoolcraft, Freeman, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - Schreckengost, Viktor, 1932 (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - Schreiber, Georges, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - Schreyer, Adolphe, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - Schrimpf, G., circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - Schroder, Fridjthof, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - Schroder, Heinrich, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - Schuler, Hans and Robert L. Harris, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 73)
  - Schultz, Harry, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 74)
  - Schultz, Hart, 1931 (Box 21, Folder 75)
  - Schumacher, William E., circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - Schumate, Ella, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 77)
  - Schutze, Anton, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 78)
  - Schutze, Eva Watson, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 79)
  - Schwalbach, Carl, 1927 (Box 21, Folder 80)
  - Schwartz, William S., 1936-1939 (Box 21, Folder 81)
  - Schwarz, Frank H., circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 82)
  - Schwaz, Maler zu, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 83)
  - Scott, Eric G., 1927 (Box 21, Folder 84)
  - Scott, Powell, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 85)
  - Scott, S., circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 86)
  - Scott, William E., circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 87)
  - Scriven, E., circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 88)
  - Seago, Edward, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 89)
  - Segonzac, Andre Dunoyer de, 1929-1941 (Box 21, Folder 90)
  - Seidel, Emory P., circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 91)
  - Seignac, G., circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 92)
  - Sekino, Junichiro, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 93)
  - Selden, Dixie, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 94)
  - Selder, Henry Bill, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 95)
  - Selfridge, Reynolds L., circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 96)
  - Sellers, J., circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 97)
  - Senex, J., circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 98)
  - Sepeshy, Zoltan, 1937 (Box 21, Folder 99)
  - Serisawa, Sueo, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 100)
  - Servas, John A., circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 101)
  - Sether, Gulbrand, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 102)
  - Seurat, Georges, 1935-1943 (Box 21, Folder 103)
  - Severini, Gino, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 104)
  - Seward, C. A., circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 105)
  - Seyffert, Leopold, 1940-1941 (Box 21, Folder 106)
  - Seymour, Ralph Fletcher, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 107)
  - Shackelford, Shelby, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 108)
  - Shackelton, K., circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 109)
  - Shahn, Ben, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 110)
  - Shannon, Charles, 1925-1941 (Box 21, Folder 111)
  - Shannon, James J., circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 112)
  - Sharp, Hill, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 113)
  - Sharp, William, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 114)
  - Sharrer, Honore, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 115)
  - Shayer, H. C., circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 116)
  - Shayer, William, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 117)
  - Shee, Martin Archer, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 118)
  - Sheeler, Charles, 1935-1940 (Box 21, Folder 119)
  - Sheets, Millard, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 120)
  - Sheffer, Glen C., circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 121)
  - Sheffers, Peter Winthrop, 1944 (Box 21, Folder 122)
  - Sheldon, Roy, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 123)
  - Shepherd, George, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 124)
  - Shepherd, J. Clinton, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 125)
  - Sherwood, Ruth, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 126)
  - Shinn, Everett, 1939-1945 (Box 21, Folder 127)
  - Shiva, Ramon, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 128)
  - Shizan, Miyata, 1930 (Box 21, Folder 129)
  - Shinable, E. R., 1930 (Box 21, Folder 130)
  - Shoemaker, Vaughn R., 1936 (Box 21, Folder 131)
  - Shonbauer, Henry, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 132)
  - Shopen, Kenneth, 1937-1940 (Box 21, Folder 133)
  - Shoshannah, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 134)
  - Shulkin, Anatol, 1932 (Box 21, Folder 135)
  - Shulz, Ada Walter, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 136)
  - Shulz, Adolph R., circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 137)
  - Shuster, Will, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 138)
  - Shute, Ben, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 139)
  - Sicard, Pierre, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 140)
  - Sichulski, Casimir, 1930 (Box 21, Folder 141)
  - Sickert, Walter, 1926-1931 (Box 21, Folder 142)
  - Sidle, Margaret, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 143)
  - Siems, Alice Littig, 1933 (Box 21, Folder 144)
  - Signac, Paul, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 145)
  - Silbert, Ben, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 146)
  - Sileikis, Michael, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 147)
  - Silva, William P., circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 148)
  - Simkhovitch, Simka, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 149)
  - Simkovits, Jeno, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 150)
  - Simmons, John, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 151)
  - Simmons, Teresa Cerutti, 1931 (Box 21, Folder 152)
  - Simmons, Will, 1931 (Box 21, Folder 153)
  - Simon, Howard, 1934 (Box 21, Folder 154)
  - Simon, J. F., circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 155)
  - Simon, Lucien, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 156)
  - Simoni, Edgardo, 1930 (Box 21, Folder 157)
  - Simpson, Bernard, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 158)
  - Simpson, Charles, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 159)
  - Simpson, Ivan F., circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 160)
  - Simpson, Maxwell, 1931 (Box 21, Folder 161)
  - Simpson, William Marx, 1930 (Box 21, Folder 162)
  - Sims, Charles, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 163)
  - Sinclair, Gerrit V., circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 164)
  - Singer, Clyde, 1935-1947 (Box 21, Folder 165)
  - Singer, William Earl, 1936 (Box 21, Folder 166)
  - Sintevis, Renee, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 167)
  - Siporin, Mitchell, 1936-1940 (Box 21, Folder 168)
  - Siquieros, Davida, circa 1888-1959 (Box 21, Folder 169)
  - Sironi, Mario, 1931 (Box 21, Folder 170)
  - Sisley, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 171)